May the schwartz be with you.
Spaceballs is a comedy, science fiction film directed by Mel Brooks.
When the nefarious Dark Helmet hatches a plan to snatch Princess Vespa and steal her planet's
air, space-bum-for-hire Lone Starr and his clueless sidekick fly to the rescue.
Along the way, they meet Yogurt, who puts Lone Starr wise to the power of
"The Schwartz." Can he master it in time to save the day?
President Skroob / Yogurt, played by Mel Brooks.
Barf, played by John Candy.
Dark Helmet, played by Rick Moranis.
Lone Starr, played by Bill Pullman.
Princess Vespa, played by Daphne Zuniga.
King Roland, played by Dick Van Patten.
Spaceballs 2 is an upcoming American space opera parody
film and the sequel to Spaceballs (1987).
It is directed by Josh Greenbaum and written by Josh
Gad, Benji Samit and Dan Hernandez.
The film sees Mel Brooks, Rick Moranis (in his first live-action film role in 30 years), Bill Pullman, George Wyner, and Daphne Zuniga
reprising their roles from the previous film, while Gad, Keke Palmer, Lewis Pullman and Anthony Carrigan join the cast.
Like its predecessor, the film will primarily be a parody of Star
Wars, but will also parody other popular media.
It is scheduled for a release in 2027.
The film explores themes of galaxy, android, space marine, laser gun, temple.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.